[
  {
    "gameId": "game-mbo76ewdntlbij4ni",
    "challengerUsername": "@omar",
    "opponentUsername": "@noha",
    "questions": [
      {
        "questionText": "alalsl",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3swur72ut2w0gn-0",
            "text": "wowlsl"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3swurkqk7bh9s4-1",
            "text": "wowll"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3swur72ut2w0gn-0",
        "id": "mbo3swur74i9b3mie",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:51:05.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "wowlso",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3tcgokbbsstvgp-0",
            "text": "wowksl"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3tcgod56r4hzou-1",
            "text": "wowll"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3tcgokbbsstvgp-0",
        "id": "mbo3tcgo2id2f8jwd",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:51:35.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "sps;s;s;",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-1749352045943k3btyq2-0",
            "text": "pss;pss;p"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-174935204594313xv87d-1",
            "text": "wps;s;"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-1749352045943wzza1i8-2",
            "text": "wps;s;"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-1749352045943hutbhd2-3",
            "text": "wpw;ps"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-174935204594313xv87d-1",
        "id": "1749352045943a9z4jv6",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:52:05.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "wksks",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3ti88681s5jlto-0",
            "text": "wowls"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3ti88c0ehvqr4v-1",
            "text": "wowl"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3ti88681s5jlto-0",
        "id": "mbo3ti88szpyp56uv",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:52:35.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "laslslsl",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3ssxam5snjptr2-0",
            "text": "slsls"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3ssxaqz4sa6dlb-1",
            "text": "slsl"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3ssxam5snjptr2-0",
        "id": "mbo3ssxarwhcg74r6",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:53:05.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "s;ls;s.s.s.",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-17493520300266mjszaz-0",
            "text": "sps;s;swls"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-1749352030026o419rvh-1",
            "text": "spslsls"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-1749352030026vzj8jee-2",
            "text": "sps;sps"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-1749352030026bfrca4p-3",
            "text": "papsls"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-1749352030026vzj8jee-2",
        "id": "1749352030026x6iedpu",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:53:35.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "slslsl",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3spzipckgs8mau-0",
            "text": "slslsl"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3spziwlfcdqgek-1",
            "text": "lwsll"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3spzipckgs8mau-0",
        "id": "mbo3spzi3egpsi0li",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:54:05.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Which of the following is considered a common side effect of the above illustrated drug\n(Trifeme /Ethinylestradiol+ Levonorgestrel)? Which of the following is considered a common side effect of the above illustrated drug\n(Trifeme /Ethinylestradiol+ Levonorgestrel)?",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-0",
            "text": "Which of the following is considered a common side effect of the above illustrated drug (Trifeme /Ethinylestradiol+ Levonorgestrel)?"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-1",
            "text": "Which of the following is considered a common side effect of the above illustrated drug (Trifeme /Ethinylestradiol+ Levonorgestrel)?"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-2",
            "text": "Which of the following is considered a common side effect of the above illustrated drug (Trifeme /Ethinylestradiol+ Levonorgestrel)?"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-3",
            "text": "Which of the following is considered a common side effect of the above illustrated drug (Trifeme /Ethinylestradiol+ Levonorgestrel)?"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-0",
        "id": "1749382612070lhi4n8o",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:54:35.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "sksks",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3tlv025bvazcdn-0",
            "text": "wowks"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3tlv05j2mlmgzf-1",
            "text": "wowk"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3tlv025bvazcdn-0",
        "id": "mbo3tlv0lchuyw3cr",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:55:05.589Z"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "wowksl",
        "type": "mcq",
        "options": [
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3sme6aak0nxept-0",
            "text": "wowlls"
          },
          {
            "id": "option-mbo3sme6iiy5tblhu-1",
            "text": "sowlsl"
          }
        ],
        "correctOptionId": "option-mbo3sme6aak0nxept-0",
        "id": "mbo3sme6a1cg45h7p",
        "startTime": "2025-06-08T21:55:35.589Z"
      }
    ],
    "status": "active",
    "createdAt": "2025-06-08T21:51:00.589Z",
    "updatedAt": "2025-06-08T21:56:33.188Z",
    "currentQuestionIndex": 0,
    "challengerAnswers": {},
    "opponentAnswers": {
      "mbo3swur74i9b3mie": {
        "questionId": "mbo3swur74i9b3mie",
        "selectedOptionId": "option-mbo3swur72ut2w0gn-0",
        "isCorrect": true,
        "timeTakenMs": 1617
      },
      "mbo3tcgo2id2f8jwd": {
        "questionId": "mbo3tcgo2id2f8jwd",
        "selectedOptionId": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "timeTakenMs": 30006
      },
      "1749352045943a9z4jv6": {
        "questionId": "1749352045943a9z4jv6",
        "selectedOptionId": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "timeTakenMs": 30047
      },
      "mbo3ti88szpyp56uv": {
        "questionId": "mbo3ti88szpyp56uv",
        "selectedOptionId": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "timeTakenMs": 30321
      },
      "mbo3ssxarwhcg74r6": {
        "questionId": "mbo3ssxarwhcg74r6",
        "selectedOptionId": "option-mbo3ssxam5snjptr2-0",
        "isCorrect": true,
        "timeTakenMs": 16566
      },
      "mbo3spzi3egpsi0li": {
        "questionId": "mbo3spzi3egpsi0li",
        "selectedOptionId": "option-mbo3spziwlfcdqgek-1",
        "isCorrect": false,
        "timeTakenMs": 6973
      },
      "1749382612070lhi4n8o": {
        "questionId": "1749382612070lhi4n8o",
        "selectedOptionId": "option-0",
        "isCorrect": true,
        "timeTakenMs": 3004
      },
      "mbo3tlv0lchuyw3cr": {
        "questionId": "mbo3tlv0lchuyw3cr",
        "selectedOptionId": "option-mbo3tlv05j2mlmgzf-1",
        "isCorrect": false,
        "timeTakenMs": 2212
      },
      "mbo3sme6a1cg45h7p": {
        "questionId": "mbo3sme6a1cg45h7p",
        "selectedOptionId": null,
        "isCorrect": false,
        "timeTakenMs": 56773
      }
    },
    "challengerScore": 0,
    "opponentScore": 4
  }
]